http://www.englertinc.com/terms-of-use-and-privacy-policy.html

Englert Inc.
Metal Roofing & Wall PanelsMetal Roofing OverviewArchitectural Metal Roof SystemsStructural Metal Roof SystemsCurved Panel Metal Roof SystemsWall Panel SystemsSoffit SystemsRetrofit FramingRoofing CoilLEED CertificationGuttersGutters OverviewK-StyleLeafGuardMicroGuardSureGuardBecome a DealerGutter CoilMachinesPortable Roll Forming MachinesRoofing MachinesGutter MachinesSeamersRoofing and Gutter Machine RepairGutter & Roofing CoilMachines OverviewArchitects/ContractorsArchitectsContractorsHome/Building Owners
Menu
Metal Roofing & Wall PanelsMetal Roofing OverviewArchitectural Metal Roof SystemsStructural Metal Roof SystemsCurved Panel Metal Roof SystemsWall Panel SystemsSoffit SystemsRetrofit FramingRoofing CoilLEED CertificationGuttersGutters OverviewK-StyleLeafGuardMicroGuardSureGuardBecome a DealerGutter CoilMachinesPortable Roll Forming MachinesRoofing MachinesGutter MachinesSeamersRoofing and Gutter Machine RepairGutter & Roofing CoilMachines OverviewArchitects/ContractorsArchitectsContractorsHome/Building Owners
1.800.englert
Terms of Use and Privacy Policy
Englert Inc. recognizes the importance our customers place on
privacy and the security of their personal information. Our goal is to
protect your personal information in every way that we interact with
you, whether it is on the telephone, in person, on the Internet, by
e-mail, by mail, or by any other means of communication.
We think it is important for you to be informed of the policies,
procedures, and security measures we have in place to safeguard your
personal and confidential information. We have developed this policy to
help you to understand the steps we take to protect your personal
information.
How We Collect Information - As part of providing services, we may obtain information about customers from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on applications, e-mails, or other forms;
Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, and others'
Information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency; and
Information that is generated electronically when you visit our website.
Accuracy
- Englert Inc. strives to keep customer
information as accurate and current as possible. If you find or believe
that any information in the possession of Englert Inc. is inaccurate,
incomplete, or outdated, please notify the Company by e-mail or in
writing. Please include your name and address as it appears on your
account statement, specify the information that you believe to be
inaccurate and include accurate information. Englert Inc. will correct
any erroneous information in a timely manner.
Security - This Company has developed strict policies
and procedures to safeguard personal information. We restrict employee
access to your sensitive personal information to a "need to know" basis.
We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply
with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic information. We
educate our employees about the importance of confidentiality and
customer privacy. We take appropriate disciplinary measures to enforce
employee privacy responsibilities and offer secure e-mail. You should
use the secure e-mail anytime you send Englert Inc. sensitive personal
information.
Privacy for Internet Users - Our commitment to
safeguard your privacy also extends to the Internet. If you are just
browsing through our website, we do not collect any personally
identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily and knowingly
provide us that information, such as when you send us an e-mail or fill
out a request for information form. If you provide us this information,
it is only used internally and in furtherance of the purpose for which
it was provided.
Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses - An IP address is a
number that is automatically assigned to your computer while on the
Internet. Web servers, the computers that "serve up" web pages,
automatically identify your computer by its IP address.
When collecting information, Englert Inc. does not link IP addresses to
anything personally identifiable, which means that a user's session
will be logged, but the user remains anonymous.
Englert Inc. may use IP addresses to audit the use of our site. They
can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when necessary for
security purposes.
What is a Cookie? - A cookie is a very small text file
sent by a web server and stored on your hard drive, your computer's
memory, or in your browser so that it can be read back later. Cookies
cannot "read" information about you from your computer or be used to
"steal" information; and cookies do not carry viruses. Cookies are a
basic way for a server to identify you (most cookies actually identify
the computer you happen to be using at the time, not you personally).
Cookies are used for many things from personalizing start up pages to
facilitating online purchases. Englert Inc. uses cookies to provide
features within the portal. They send a "Web Trends" cookie to all
Portal visitors in order to help us collect general information on all
portal visitors. This cookie is sent to your computer hard drive and
provides us information such as when you accessed our site, which pages
you accessed in the portal, and what Internet provider you used when you
accessed our site. The information collected through this cookie is not
personally identifiable and is only used for statistical purposes to
assist in our planning process and our marketing program.
Disclosure of Information
We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our
customers, former customers, web site visitors or portal visitors to
anyone, except as permitted by law.
In the future, we may disclose a portion of the aggregate customer
information we collect on the portal to companies that perform marketing
services on our behalf.
We will provide you an opt-in or opt-out notice if required by law.
E-Mail Policies
In the future we may send you e-mail notices for certain disclosures if
you choose to accept electronic disclosures or statements. We may also
send you e-mails to market our products and services that may of
interest to you. We will always provide you an opportunity to opt-out of
these advertising promotions if required by law.
Free Englert Roofing Mobile App Download:
Easy access to all Englert brochures and catalogs, a color selector for both roofing and gutter colors, standing seam metal roof panel profiles, and a convenient coil calculator to assist in estimating and completing your particular project.
App Sore
Google Play
Have a Question?
1.800.ENGLERT
PHOTO GALLERYROOF COLOR VISUALIZERAWARD WINNING PROJECTSPaperless InvoicesTestimonials
Search
Facebook
Youtube
Google Plus
About EnglertContact UsNews & EventsCareersAccessibilityBLOGAIA/CEU Courses
Copyright 2018 - Englert Inc. - All rights reserved - Designed and Developed - Sitemap - Terms & Privacy
